http://www.countrytabs.com/policy/privacy.asp

2,751 bands | 35,343 songs
Search:
Register FREE! | Login
Browse Songs:
Z
Browse Bands:
CountryTabs.com Privacy Policy
By accessing or using the CountryTabs.com Web site, you agree to the terms of the CountryTabs.com Privacy Policy, as outlined below. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site.
Collection of Personal Information
When you engage in certain activities on this site, such as registering, joining the newsletter, or voting for a poll, CountryTabs.com may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, CountryTabs.com may require that you provide us personal information, such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, and other personal identifying information.
When you submit personal information to CountryTabs.com, you understand and agree that CountryTabs.com and its subsidiaries, affiliates and trusted vendors may transfer, store, and process your customer profile in any of the countries in which CountryTabs.com and its affiliates maintain offices, including without limitation, the United States.
CountryTabs.com collects this information in order to record and support your participation in the activities you select. CountryTabs.com uses information that you provide as part of our effort to keep you informed about new tabs, special offers, and other CountryTabs.com events.
CountryTabs.com recognizes and appreciates the importance of responsible use of this information. If you do not want the information you provide to CountryTabs.com to be used to inform you of other new tabs and events from CountryTabs.com, and you indicate this preference when you provide the information to CountryTabs.com, CountryTabs.com will honor your preference.
Use of Cookies
When you visit CountryTabs.com, you can surf the site anonymously and access the majority of the site without revealing your identity. In order to improve our site, we may use "cookies" to track your visit. A cookie is small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a Web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. It functions as your identification card, recording your user name, password, and date of visits. It cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.
Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. (For some Web pages that require an authorization, cookies are not optional. Users choosing not to accept cookies will probably not be able to access those pages.)
While CountryTabs.com uses cookies to track your visit, and our Web servers automatically log the IP/Internet address of your computer, this information does not identify you personally and you remain anonymous unless you have otherwise provided CountryTabs.com with personal information.
Third Party Advertising & Cookies
We partner with third party ad networks and allows such networks to use cookies to collect non-personally identifiable data for targeting and serving ads. Users can opt-out of this behavioral targeting by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative's consumer page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp
Home |
FAQs |
Privacy |
Terms |
Advertise |
Contact
Top 100 Tab Sites
